爸爸要我们继承他的事业
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off.
救助他人 猎杀恶魔 家族事业
Saving people, hunting things. Family business.
爸爸最后一次猎鬼时有个搭档
My dad had a partner on his last hunt.
那个家伙搞砸了 害我爸被杀
Guy screwed up, got my dad killed.
- 那跟我们有什么… - 那家伙就是你爸爸 迪恩
- What does this have to do? - It was your father, Dean.
也许这就是魔鬼想要的 逼迫我们 想方设法让我们崩溃
Maybe that's what the demon's doing. Pushing us. Finding ways to break us.
我叫梅格 她被附身了
I'm Meg. She's possessed.
魔鬼附在人类身上
That's a human possessed by a demon.
"索罗门之匙" 能困住魔鬼 封住他们的力量
The key of Solomon. You get a demon in one, they're trapped.
爸爸死前告诉了我一些事 关于你的
Before Dad died, he told me something, something about you.
他说我得救你 如果不能 就得杀了你
He said that I had to save you. That if I couldn't, I'd have to kill you.
他知道魔鬼对我的安排是什么吗？
Did he know the demon's plans?
- 我会变成邪恶的一方还是怎么？- 我没那么说过
- Am I supposed to go dark side? - I never said that.
你要是不小心点 总有一天得杀了我 迪恩
Jeez, you're not careful, you will have to waste me one day, Dean.
埃伦 还是我
Ellen. It's me again.
有他的消息吗？
Any chance you've heard from him?
简直像那时候到处找我爸一样
I swear, it's like looking for my dad all over again.
我都快急疯了
I'm losing my mind here.
我给他打过很多次电话 每次都是留言
No, I've called him a thousand times. Nothing but voice mail.
我不知道他去哪儿了 也不知道为什么
I don't know where he went or why.
萨姆就那么消失了
Sam's just gone.
等会儿
Hang on.
萨姆 你跑哪儿去了 你没事吧？
Sammy? Where the hell are you? Are you okay?
嘿 嘿 嘿 冷静点 你在哪儿？
Hey, hey, hey, calm down. Where are you?
好了 别动 我马上就到
All right, don't move. I'm on my way.
萨姆 是我
Sam, it's me.
萨姆
Sam?
萨姆？
嘿
Hey.
嗨 迪恩
Hey, Dean.
你受伤了？
Are you bleeding?
我洗不掉
I tried to wash it off.
哦 天
Oh, my God.
不是我的血
I don't think it's my blood.
- 那是谁的？- 不知道
- Whose is it? - I don't know.
萨姆 到底怎么回事？
Sam, what the hell happened?
迪恩…
Dean.
我什么都想不起来了
I don't remember anything.
[邪恶力量 第2季第14集]
有什么发现吗？
What'd you find out?
你两天前以理查德·山伯拉的名字入住
You checked in two days ago, under the name Richard Sambora.
最恐怖的你居然是Bon Jovi乐队吉他手理查德·山伯拉的迷
I think the scariest part about this is that you're a Bon Jovi fan.
迪恩
Dean.
你的房间一直很平静 没人注意到什么异常情况
Your room's been quiet. Nobody noticed anything unusual.
你是说没人看见我满身是血地走来走去？
You mean no one saw me walking around covered in blood?
- 对 就是这个意思 - 那我是怎么跑到这儿来的 迪恩？
- Yeah, that's what I mean. - Then how did I get here, Dean?
- 我怎么了？- 不知道
- What happened to me? - I don't know, all right?
但你没事就好
But you're okay, that's what matters.
- 其他的我们都能应付 - 是吗？
- Everything else we can deal with. - Oh, really?
- 要是我伤了谁怎么办？或者更糟 - 萨姆
- What if I hurt someone? Or worse. - Sam.
也许这就是爸爸警告你的原因
What if this is what Dad warned you about?
好了 别妄下结论
Hey, whoa, whoa. Let's not jump the gun here.
我们不知道出了什么事
We don't know what happened.
得像其他"工作"一样处理
We just gotta treat this like any job.
你记得的最后一件事是什么？
What's the last thing you remember?
我和你 在西德克萨斯的一个旅馆
It's me and you in that motel room in West Texas.
- 我们出门买汉堡 - 西德克萨斯？那是一周以前的事了
- I went out to grab some burgers and... - West Texas? That was over a week ago.
没错
That's it.
然后就发现 自己坐在这儿…
Next thing I knew, I was sitting here.
一身是血
Bloody.
- 好像睡了一整个月一样 - 好了 让我们回溯一下你的行动
- It felt like I'd been asleep for a month. - Okay. Retrace your steps.
旅馆老板说你昨天下午出门以后
The manager said you left yesterday afternoon.
就没见你回来
They never saw you come back so...
嘿
Hey.
想起什么了？
Recognize anything?
没什么
Not really.
等等
Wait.
- 什么？- 我想我来过这儿
- What? - I think I was here.
你想起来了？
Do you remember?
也不是 只是…
Not really. It just...
有种熟悉的感觉 你知道
It feels familiar, you know?
试试那个
Try that one.
- 对 - 好
- Yeah. - Okay.
等一下
Wait.
别跟我说你居然偷了这种车
Oh, please tell me you didn't steal this.
更多的血
More blood.
萨姆 后座
Sam, back seat.
你觉得我会不会用在什么人身上了？
You think I used this on someone?
我什么都不知道
I'm not thinking anything.
好吧 这可有点古怪了
Okay, now this is disturbing.
好了 老弟 这怎么可能是你的 说不定是其他人
Come on, this couldn't have been you. Had to have been someone else.
一个 呃 抽薄荷烟的家伙
Somebody who, uh, smokes menthols.
嘿
Hey.
加油站的收据 就在不远的一个镇
A gas receipt, few towns over.
10加仑油的收据 2号油泵
All right, the receipt's for 10 gallons at pump number two.
有没有起鸡皮疙瘩？
You getting any goose bumps yet?
"天哪 看起来太熟悉了" 这类的感觉？
"God, this looks familiar, " déjà-vu vibes?
也许里面那人记得你
Maybe someone inside will remember you.
来吧
Come on.
你 滚出去 马上 我要报警了
You, out of here, now. I'm calling the cops.
- 你说的是他？- 没错 就是他
- You talking to him? - Yeah, I'm talking to him.
这混蛋昨天喝得烂醉 从冰箱里抓起一瓶啤酒就开始喝
Jerk comes in yesterday, stinking drunk. Grabs a 40 from the fridge, starts chugging.
他？你居然喝麦芽酒？
This guy? You drinking malt liquor?
还用瓶子敲了我的头
Not after he whipped the bottle at my frigging head.
- 这家伙？- 怎么了 难道我说的是鸟语？
- This guy? - What, am I speaking Urdu?
如果我干了什么 真的很抱歉
I'm sorry if I did anything
你最好一边走一边编你的故事 警察5分钟就到
Tell your story walking, pal. Okay? Po-po will be here in five.
等会儿 他会走的 他会走的 把电话放下
Wait, wait. He's leaving, he's leaving. Put the phone down.
- 萨姆 回车里等着 - 可是 迪恩
- Sam, go wait in the car. - But, Dean...
回车里等我
Go wait in the car.
好了 我只想跟你说几句话 行吗
Hey, look, I just wanna talk to you, that's it, okay?
他昨天出门后朝哪个方向走了？
When he took off, which way did he go?
- 干吗不问他？- 因为我在问你
- Why don't you ask him? - I'm asking you.
求你了 算是帮我一个大忙好不好
Please. You'd be doing me a huge favor.
哦 帮你的忙 好啊 我就是以此为生的
Oh, do you a favor? Well, that is what I live for.
说起来 你的同伴还没付酒钱呢
You know, your buddy didn't pay for the booze...
还有他抽的烟 点烟的方式也是违法的
or the smokes, which he also illegally lit up.
- 你看见他抽烟？- 没错 简直像个烟囱
- You saw him smoking? - Yeah. Guy's a chimney.
这些 嗯…
This, uh, ought to cover it.
应该够了 呃 我想起来了
Mm. It's, uh... It's coming back to me now.
他拿了两包
He took two packs.
当然了
Of course he did.
他顺着北边的71号路 直接出城了
He went north on Route 71. Straight out of town.
你到底怎么回事 萨姆 嗯？
What's going on with you, Sam? Hmm?
抽烟 朝别人乱挥酒瓶子
Because smoking, throwing bottles at people...
听起来更像我干的
I mean, that sounds more like me than you.
迪恩 等一下 等会儿 这儿 上那条路
Dean, wait. Right here. Turn down that road.
- 什么？- 不知道为什么 我就是知道
- What? - I don't know how I know. I just do.
不管这里住的是谁 看来不喜欢惊喜
Whoever lives here, I'd say they don't like surprises.
该敲门吗？
Should we knock?
我想应该
Yeah. I guess.
嘿 迪恩
Hey, Dean.
奇怪的是警察居然没出现
I'm surprised the cops didn't show.
这种地方应该有警报系统
Place like this, you'd think it'd have an alarm.
是啊 你说的没错
Yeah, you would.
开灯
Hit the lights.
- 迪恩 是我干的 - 我们还不知道
- Dean, I did this. - We don't know that.
你还要什么证据？
What else do you need?
你怎么解释那车子 刀 还有血？
How else do you explain the car, the knife, the blood?
我不知道 老弟 你干吗不告诉我？
I don't know, man. Why don't you tell me?
就算是你干的 也肯定有什么原因
Even if you did do this, I'm sure you had a reason.
比如自卫 他是个坏家伙之类的
You know: self-defense, uh, he was a bad son of a bitch, something.
没有身份证
He didn't have any ID.
- 把你的开锁器给我 - 什么？
- I need your lock pick. - What?
给我开锁器
I need your lock pick.
这家伙要不是个恐怖分子 要不就是个猎手
Either this guy's a Unabomber or a hunter.
迪恩 我杀了个猎手
Dean, I think I killed a hunter.
我们很快就能知道了
Let's find out.
就是这儿了
Here we go.
录像要怎么消除？
How do you erase this, huh?
萨姆 快点 帮把手
Sam, come on. I need your help.
我杀了他 迪恩
I killed him, Dean.
破门而入 杀了他
I just broke in and killed him.
听我说 不管他是谁 他是个猎手
Listen to me. Whoever this guy is, he's a hunter.
就是说他的同伴会到处寻找凶手
Other hunters are gonna come looking for his killer.
就是说 我们得销毁所有线索 明白吗？
Which means we gotta cover our tracks, okay?
他叫史提夫·万德尔
His name was Steve Wandel.
这是他女儿的信
This is a letter from his daughter.
把指纹擦干净 我们走了
Wipe your prints. Then we go.
好了 咱们休息几个小时 然后上路离开这里
All right, we get a couple hours of sleep, then put this place in our rear-view mirror.
我知道这很糟糕
Look, I know this is bad, okay?
你得振作起来
You gotta snap out of it.
萨姆 说话啊
Sam, say something.
睡一觉 然后早上上路？
We should get some sleep and leave in the morning?
谋杀 迪恩 那是我干的
Murder, Dean. That's what I did.
也许是 嘿 我们又不知道 也许是变形怪
Maybe, okay? Hey, we don't know-Shapeshifter.
哦 算了吧 你明知道不是 你也看了录像带
Come on. You know it wasn't. You saw the tape.
- 眼睛没有反光 也没有变形 - 可那不是你
- There was no eye flare, no distortion. - But it wasn't you.
也许那个是你 但不是真正的你
All right. Yeah, it might've been you, but it wasn't you.
我想是的
I think it was.
只是你不知道
I think maybe more than you know.
这话什么意思？
What the hell does that mean?
过去几个星期里 我总是…
For the last few weeks, I've been having...
有这种感觉
I've been having these feelings.
- 什么感觉？- 愤怒…
- What feelings? - Rage.
憎恨
Hate.
我没法抑制
And I can't stop it.
变得越来越糟 一天天的变得更严重
It just gets worse. Day by day, it gets worse.
你没告诉过我
You never told me this.
我不想吓着你
I didn't wanna scare you.
保密工作做的真不错
Well, bang-up job on that.
迪恩 黄眼睛的魔鬼 你知道他对我有所安排
Dean, the Yellow-Eyed Demon, you know he has plans for me.
我们也都知道 他曾经把其他的孩子变成凶手
We know he's turned other children into killers before too.
- 除了你自己 没人能控制你 - 那可不一定 迪恩
- No one can control you but you. - Doesn't seem like that.
不管怎么努力
It feels like no matter what I do, slowly but surely...
- 我都在确实慢慢地变成 - 什么？
- ...I'm just becoming. - What?
我应该变成的东西
Who I'm meant to be.
你自己也说过 迪恩 我得接受自己的命运
You said it once yourself. I gotta face up to who I am.
- 我不是那个意思 - 但这话没错 你知道的
- I didn't meant this. - But it's still true. You know that.
爸爸也知道 所以他才告诉你
Dad knew that too. That's why he told you...
- 如果事情变成这样 - 闭嘴 萨姆
- ...if it ever came to this. - Shut up, Sam.
迪恩 你答应过他的
Dean, you promised him.
你也答应过我的
You promised me.
不
No.
听我说
Listen to me.
我们会想办法解决的 好吗？我是说 总有办法 对吧？
We're gonna figure this out, okay? I mean, there's gotta be a way, right?
没错
Yeah, there is.
我不想再伤害别人了
I don't wanna hurt anyone else.
特别是你
I don't wanna hurt you.
你不会的
You won't.
不管是什么 你都能打败它
Whatever this is, you can fight it.
不 我不能
No. I can't.
不可能永远这样
Not forever.
拿着 这是你该做的
Here, you gotta do it.
知道吗 我那么努力的保护你
You know, I've tried so hard to keep you safe.
我知道
I know.
我做不到
I can't.
死也不干
I'd rather die.
不
No.
你会活着
You'll live.
活着 后悔没杀了我
You'll live to regret this.
退房时间过了
It's past your checkout.
- 什么？- 退房时间过了
- What? - It's past checkout...
这儿有一对夫妇要住你的房间
and I have a couple here who need your room.
是的 他们是的
Oh, yeah, I'll bet they do.
- 几点了？- 12点半
- What time is it? - Twelve thirty.
跟我一起的那个家伙 你看到他了吗？
The guy that was with me, have you seen him?
他天亮之前开着你的车走了 你真该和他一起走
He left before dawn in your car. You should've gone with him...
现在你得多交钱了
because now I'm gonna have to charge you extra.
- 哦 混蛋 - 这是规定 先生
- Oh, son of a bitch. - That's just the policy, sir.
我要用你的电脑
I need to use your computer.
我干嘛要让你用我的电脑？
Why would I let you use my computer?
嗨 呃 很抱歉打扰你
Hi, uh, so sorry to bother you...
但 呃 我儿子昨天晚上偷偷溜出家门
but, uh, my son snuck out of the house last night...
呃 去看贾斯汀·汀布莱克的演唱会
and, uh, went to a Justin Timberlake concert.
什么？
What?
对 对 贾斯汀是很有才能
Yeah, Justin is quite the triple threat.
嗯 总之 他还没回家 我有点担心了
Uh, anyway, he's not back yet and I'm just-I'm starting to worry.
对 是的 男孩子总有一天要长大
Right, boys will be boys.
可萨姆有… 糖尿病 如果不及时打胰岛素
But see, Sammy is a, uh, a diabetic and, uh, if he doesn't get his insulin...
我 我得找到他
then I just-I have to find him.
求你了
Please. I'm begging you.
不不不 我正在网上
Yeah, no, no, no. I'm on the website right now.
只要激活他手机的GPS就行
I just need to activate the GPS in his cell phone.
对 找到了 德卢斯 明尼苏达州
Yeah, right there. Duluth, Minnesota.
是啊 为了演唱会跑这么远的
Yeah, that is a long way to go for a concert.
非常感谢
I appreciate your help.
晚安 谢谢
Good night, thank you.
不好意思 关门了
Sorry, we're closing up.
上路之前再来一杯行吗？
How about just one for the road?
真没想到会是你
You're about the last person I'd expect to see.
是啊…
Well...
看来我总是出人意料
guess I'm full of surprises.
能来杯啤酒吗？
So can I get a beer?
当然 啤酒一瓶
Sure, one beer.
你怎么找到我的？
So how'd you find me?
呃 我们的工作就是这样的
Well, uh, it's kind of what we do, you know?
- 说到"我们" 迪恩在哪儿？- 他来不了
- Speaking of we, where's Dean? - He couldn't make it.
那你在这儿干什么 萨姆？
So, what are you doing here, Sam?
我们好像也没那么熟？
I mean, we didn't exactly part on the best of terms.
没错
Right. Um...
所以我才来这儿
That's why I'm here.
想看看我们能不能消除误会
I kind of-I wanted to see if we could square things, you know?
看起来挺疼的
That looks like it hurts.
不 不 只是…
No. No, just...
被火炉烫了一下
had a run-in with a hot stove.
你刚才说什么消除误会？
So you were saying something about squaring things?
对
Yeah. Uh...
我知道你对我爸的看法
Look, I know how you feel about my dad.
也不能怪你
And I can't say I blame you.
他鬼迷心窍
He was obsessed.
满脑子只想着猎魔
Consumed with hunting.
根本不管有谁陷入危险
And he didn't care who got caught in the crossfire.
我想也包括你爸爸
And I guess that included your dad.
但那是我爸
But that was my father.
不是我
That's not me.
那迪恩呢？
What about Dean?
这个嘛 迪恩比我更像我爸 但他…
Well, Dean's more like my father than I am, but he-
好家伙…
Boy.
你真的迷上他了 是不是？
You're really carrying a torch for him, aren't you?
你是默认了
I'll take that as a yes.
太糟了
It's too bad.
因为 你看 迪恩他是喜欢你 但…
Because see Dean, he likes you, sure...
不是你想要的那种喜欢
but not in the way you'd want. I mean
我是说 也许像对小妹妹一样 但是爱情
Maybe as kind of a little sister, you know, but romance?
别做梦了
That's just out of the question.
他把你当成黄毛丫头 知道吗？
He kind of thinks you're a schoolgirl, you know?
我不是想让你伤心 乔
I'm not trying to hurt you, Jo, I'd
- 我这么说是因为我关心你 - 你真好心 萨姆
- I'm telling you because I care. - That's real kind of you, Sam.
我是说真的
I mean it.
我很在意你
I care about you a lot.
萨姆 怎么了？
Sam, what's going on?
我们可以更进一步 乔
I could be more to you, Jo.
也许你该走了
Maybe you should leave.
好吧
Okay.
萨姆 放开我 萨姆 放手 放手
Sam, get off me. Sam, get off me. Let go.
乔 乔 乔
Jo, Jo, Jo.
萨姆 求你了 别这样 求你了
Sam, no. Please. Please.
本来不用这样的
It didn't have to be this way.
也许没别的办法
Or maybe it did. Heh.
到底怎么回事？你干嘛？
What the hell's going on? What are you doing?
关于你爸的死 你妈妈是怎么跟你说的？
So, what exactly did your mom tell you about how your dad died?
你不是萨姆
You're not Sam.
别那么肯定 回答我的问题…
Don't be so sure about that. Answer the question.
说啊
Come on.
是我啊
It's me.
你可以告诉我任何事 你知道的
You can tell me anything, you know that.
回答问题
Answer the question.
- 好吧 - 好吧
- Fine. - Fine.
我们的爸爸在加利福尼亚
Our dads were in California.
魔鬼门水库
Devil's Gate Reservoir.
设了个陷阱给什么再生侠之类的妖怪？
They were setting a trap for some kind of hellspawn.
约翰埋伏起来 我爸爸当诱饵
John was hiding, waiting. And my dad was bait.
真是约翰的一贯风格
That's just like John.
哦 我打赌他把比尔当成鱼饵了
Oh, I bet he dangled Bill like meat on a hook.
然后呢？
Then what?
那个怪物出现了
Then the thing showed up.
约翰太急躁了
John got too eager.
他过早出击 害我爸爸孤立无援
Jumped out too soon. Got my dad exposed out in the open.
那东西转身…
The thing turned around...
杀了他
and killed him.
不够准确
Not quite.
什么？
What?
什么？哦
What? Oh.
它只是弄伤了他
You see, it hurt him.
没有杀死他
It didn't kill him.
你真的不知道真相 对吧
You really don't know the truth, do you?
- 我打赌你妈妈也不知道 - 知道什么？
- I bet your mom doesn't either. - Know what?
比尔他…
You see, Bill...
被开膛破肚
was all clawed up.
内脏都流出来了
Was holding his insides in his hands.
一边吐血. -. -
He was gurgling...
一边祈求着再见你和埃伦一面
and praying to see you and Ellen one more time.
于是我爸爸…
So my dad...
就杀了他
killed him.
像了结国病狗一样结束了他的痛苦
Put him out of his misery like a sick dog.
- 你骗人 - 我没有 是真的
- You're lying. - I'm not. It's true.
我老爸一枪爆了你老爸的头
My daddy shot your daddy in the head.
- 你怎么知道这些事？- 我听说的
- How could you know that? - I hear things.
- 你为什么这么对我？- 有其父必有其女
- Why are you doing this to me? - Like daddy, like daughter.
你是个诱饵 张嘴
You're bait. Open up.
乖孩子
That's a girl.
萨姆
Sam!
我求你制止我的 迪恩
I begged you to stop me, Dean.
- 妈的 快放下刀 - 告诉过你我做不到
- Put the knife down, damn it. - I told you, I can't fight it!
我头疼得像要烧起来了
My head feels like it's on fire, all right?
迪恩 杀了我 要不我就杀了她
Dean. Kill me or I'm gonna kill her.
求你了 帮帮我吧
Please. You'd be doing me a favor.
开枪
Shoot me.
Shoot me!
不 萨姆 别这样
No, Sammy. Come on.
你有什么毛病 迪恩？
What the hell's wrong with you, Dean?
你就那么害怕孤独 宁可让乔去死？
Are you that scared of being alone that you'd rather let Jo die?
这是圣水 混蛋魔鬼
It's holy water, you demonic son of a bitch.
他被附身了？
He was possessed?
迪恩
Dean!
- 那么你是谁？- 我有很多名字
- So who are you? I got lots of names.
你是在萨姆失踪的时候附身的 是吗？
You've been in Sam since he disappeared, haven't you?
看看你以为萨姆杀人时的表情
You should've seen your face when you thought he murdered that guy.
小可怜
Pathetic.
你为什么不杀我？机会多的是
Why didn't you kill me? You had a dozen chances.
不 那样解决你太容易了 有什么乐趣何言啊？
No, that would've been too easy. Where's the fun in that?
知道吧 这是个测试
You see, this was a test.
看你能忍受萨姆坏到什么程度才会下手
Wanted to see if I could push you far enough to waste Sam.
早该料到你没这个胆
Should've known you wouldn't have the sack.
总之 游戏结束了
Anyway, fun's over now.
哦 但愿你想好如何脱身
Oh, well, I hope you got your kicks.
- 否则你得偿还所作的一切 - 怎么还？你根本伤不了我
- You're gonna pay hell for this. - How? You can't hurt me.
不愿伤害你心爱的老弟的话
Not without hurting your little brother.
我觉得死的会是你 迪恩
See, I think you're gonna die, Dean.
你和其他的猎手我都能找到
You and every other hunter I can find.
只要看见萨姆清澈无辜的眼神
One look at Sam's dewy, sensitive eyes...
是人都会让他进屋的
they'll let me right in their door.
我是迪恩 请留下口讯
This is Dean, leave a message.
迪恩
Dean?
Dean.
放松点
Take it easy.
- 萨姆在哪？- 我不知道 我一直在找你
- Where's Sam? - I don't know. I've been looking for you.
来吧 起来
Come on. Get up.
好了
Unh! Okay.
别像小孩那样怕疼 天哪
Don't be a baby. Oh, God.
好了 就快
All right, almost.
好了 拿出来了
All right, got it. Got it.
- 天哪 你简直是个屠夫 - 多谢夸奖
- God, you're a butcher. - You're welcome.
好了没有？
All right, are we done?
你就不能闭嘴好让我包扎伤口？
Would you give me two minutes to patch you up?
流血过多死了还怎么救萨姆
You can't help Sam if you're bleeding to death.
你怎么知道他被附身？
So how did you know that he was possessed?
我不知道 只是感觉那肯定不是他
Ah! Uh, I didn't. I just knew that it couldn't have been him.
- 嘿 迪恩 - 什么
- Hey, Dean. - Yeah?
我知道恶魔一向说谎话 但有没有偶尔说真话的时候？
I know demons lie, but do they ever tell the truth too?
有时 我猜是的
Yeah, sometimes, I guess.
特别知道真话会刺激得你发狂的时候
Especially if they know it'll mess with your head.
为什么这么问？
Why do you ask?
没什么
Nothing.
不要紧
It doesn't matter.
那么 你觉得他之后会去哪？
So do you have any idea where he's headed to next?
就目前而言 他会去找离这最近的猎手
Well, so far, he's been going after the nearest hunter.
我知道最近的一个在南达科他州
So the closest one I know is in South Dakota.
包好了 我们走
Okay, good. I'm done. Let's go.
你不能去
You're not coming.
为什么不能？我已经被卷进来了
The hell I'm not. I'm a part of this now.
一言难尽
I can't say it more plain than this:
你要是跟来我还要时刻担心你
You try and follow me and I'll tie you back to that post and leave you.
这是我的事 不能让你因此受到伤害
This is my fight. I'm not getting your blood on my hands.
这就是原因
That's just how it's gonna be.
等等
Wait.
接着
Here.
吃点这个 用来止疼
Take these. They'll help with the pain.
多谢
Thanks.
晚点打电话给你 好吗？
I'll call you later, okay?
不 你不会了
No, you won't.
该死的
Damn it.
- 萨姆 - 嘿 鲍比
- Sam. - Hey, Bobby.
好久不见
It's been a while.
进来
Come on in.
什么风把你吹到这来了？
So, what brings you?
附近有个活儿 所以来和你打声招呼
Working a job nearby and I thought I'd stop in to say hey.
迪恩在哪？
Where's Dean?
在某处和女孩缠绵呢
Holed up somewhere with a girl and a 12 pack.
哦 真的？
Oh, yeah?
她很辣？
Is she pretty?
谁说不是 估计还没尽兴
You ask me, he's in way over his head.
很高兴见到你
Well, it's good to see you.
敬约翰
To John.
敬爸爸
To Dad.
你做了什么？
What'd you do?
在啤酒里加了点圣水
A little holy water in your beer.
萨姆绝不会有事
Sam never would've noticed.
但你不是萨姆 对吗？
But then, you're not Sam, are you?
休想引骗子上钩
Don't try to con a con man.
嘿
Hey. Unh.
迪恩
Dean.
从死亡边缘爬回来了
Back from the dead.
就像从前那样 不是吗？
Getting to be a regular thing for you, isn't it?
就像只蟑螂
Like a cockroach.
你这自以为是的家伙敢紧滚出来
How about I smack that smart-ass out of your mouth?
小心点
Oh, careful now.
- 不然会伤了这副皮囊 - 哦 别担心 这样不会太伤萨姆
- Wouldn't wanna bruise this fine packaging. - Don't worry. This isn't gonna hurt Sam.
你就另当别论了…
You, on the other hand-
现在愿意开口了吗？
Feel like talking now?
萨姆仍是受我控制的肉身
Sam's still my meat puppet.
- 我可以让他咬断自己的舌头 - 不 你呆不长了
- I'll make him bite off his tongue. - No. You won't be in him long enough.
鲍比
Bobby.
看见了 你这婊子养的 不管你有什么计划
See, whatever bitch-boy master plan you demons are cooking up...
都不许利用萨姆
you're not getting Sam.
明白么？
You understand me?
因为我解决掉你们每一个
Because I'm gonna kill every one of you first.
你真以为这是我们的
You really think that's what this is about?
计划吗？
The master plan?
我根本不在乎什么计划
I don't give a rat's ass about the master plan.
噢
Oops.
看来不起作用
Doesn't seem to be working.
我倒学了点新玩意儿
See, I learned a few new tricks.
这不像是附身 怎么回事 鲍比？
This isn't going like I pictured. What's going on, Bobby?
这是个封魔咒
It's a binding link.
就像把锁
It's like a lock.
把他自己封在萨姆身体里
He's locked himself inside Sam's body.
- 我们现在怎么办？- 我也不知道
- What the hell do we do? - I don't know.
现在 好多了
There. That's better.
当人们想描述最糟糕的事情…
You know when people wanna describe the worst possible thing?
他们都会用地狱来形容
They say it's "like hell."
哦 那么说是有原因的
Well, there's a reason for that.
地狱就像 嗯… . -
Hell is like a...
确实是地狱 即使对魔鬼而言也是
Well, it's like hell. Even for demons.
那是一个由血肉和恐惧
It's a prison made of bone and flesh...
筑成的牢笼
and blood and fear.
你把我打了回去
And you sent me back there.
- 梅格 - 不…
- Meg? - No.
不再是了
Not anymore.
我现在是萨姆
Now I'm Sam.
顺便说一句…
By the way...
我见到了你父亲 他向你问好
I saw your dad there. He says, "Howdy."
支持我撑下去的是一旦某天我能爬出来
All that I had to hold onto was that I would climb out one day.
就要把你折磨得痛不欲生
And then I was gonna torture you.
一点一点的折磨你 就像把虫子的翅膀一片一片扯下来那样
Nice and slow, like pulling the wings off an insect.
但是不论我怎么对你
But whatever I do to you...
都不及你内心的悔恨 对吗？
it's nothing compared to what you do to yourself, is it?
我能从你的眼睛里看出来 迪恩
I can see it in your eyes, Dean. You're worthless.
你是个废物 连自己老爸都救不了
You couldn't save your dad.
而且内心深处
And deep down...
你也清楚挽救不了你的弟弟
you know that you can't save your brother.
没有你他们会过的更好
They'd have been better off without you.
萨姆？
Sammy?
我错过什么了？
Did I miss anything?
顺便说一句 你看起来糟透了 迪恩
By the way, you really look like crap, Dean.
是啊 拜你所赐
Yeah, right back at you.
那是什么 鲍比？
What is it, Bobby?
你们俩知道叫史提夫·万德尔的猎手吗？
You boys ever hear of a hunter named Steve Wandel?
为什么问这个？
Why do you ask?
从朋友那听说 万德尔死了
Just heard from a friend. Wandel's dead.
在家里被杀了
Murdered in his own house.
你们不知道这事
You wouldn't know anything about that?
没有 从未听过这人
No, sir. Never heard of the guy.
- 迪恩 - 那好 继续装作不知道
- Dean. - Good. Keep it that way.
万德尔的兄弟正在到处查找线索
Wandel's buddies are looking for someone or something to string up.
他们追得很紧 (一旦抓住谁)可没机会解释
They're not gonna slow down to listen to reason.
你明白我的意思吗？
You understand what I'm saying?
我们最好快上路吧
We better hit the road.
要是你还记得我们车停哪里了
If you can remember where we parked the car.
给你 拿着
Here. Take these.
- 这是什么？- 符咒
- What are they? - Charms.
可以阻止附身
They'll fend off possession.
恶魔还在游荡 能防止它再次附身
That demon's still out there. This'll stop it from getting back up in you.
- 有点暧昧… 但是 谢谢你 - 不客气
- That sounds vaguely dirty, but thanks. You're welcome.
你们俩最好小心点
You boys be careful now.
你也是
You too.
你没事吧？
You okay?
萨姆？
Sam.
你没被附身吧？
Is that you in there?
我某些本性被唤醒了 迪恩
I was awake for some of it, Dean.
我看见了自己亲手杀了万德尔
I watched myself kill Wandel with my own two hands.
看到了他眼中生命之光渐渐消逝
I saw the light go out in his eyes.
那一定很可怕
That must've been awful.
我不是说这个
That's not my point.
我差点也对乔下手
I almost carved up Jo too.
但不论我做了什么你都不会开枪
But no matter what I did, you wouldn't shoot.
我没做错 萨姆 那不是你
It was the right move, Sam. It wasn't you.
是 这次是
Yeah, this time.
那下次怎么办？
What about next time?
萨姆 爸爸嘱咐我要杀你
Sam, when Dad told me that I might have to kill you...
那是在不得已得情形下
it was only if I couldn't save you.
如今 即使最坏的情况发生了 我还是要救你
Now, if it's the last thing I do, I'm gonna save you.
- 什么？- 没什么
- What? - Nothing.
迪恩 什么？
Dean, what?
老弟 你居然… 让那小妞整整赖在身上一周
Dude, you, like, full-on had a girl inside you for, like, a whole week.
真够下流的
That's pretty naughty.